Guide to the Records of the History Department of the Faculty of Arts and Science 1926-1978 (Bulk 1960-1970) RG 21.3 RG 21.3
New York University Archives
- Series I: Administrative Records
  - Baldwin, Prof. Marshall W, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Baltzly, Prof. Alexander, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Bayor, Prof. Ronald, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Binks, Carol, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Beaumont, Prof. Andre A, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Beckman, Prof. George, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Berger, Ira, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Berstein, Prof. Harry, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Bindler, Norman, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Blane, Prof. Andrew Q., 1973 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Blassingame, Mr. Lurton W., undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Bloom, Prof. Steven, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Blustain, Prof. Jonah, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Bodayia, Mr. Steven, undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Brandes, Prof. Joseph, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Bray-Thorton, Mr. Virginius, III, undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Brown, Prof. L. Carl, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Bujarski, Dr. George T., undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Caiati, Vito, undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Calahan, Prof. North, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Cammett, Prof. John M., 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Cannistraro, Prof. Phillip, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Chapman, Mr. Robert, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Chill, Prof. Emanual, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Cliadakis, Mr. Harry, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Cohen, Mr. William, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Collier, Prof. Christopher, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Comstock, Prof. George, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Cooper, Sandi, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Cortez-Conde, Roberto, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Crane, Elaine, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Crofts, Dr. Daniel W., 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Cunsolo, Prof. Ronald S., 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Danforth, Brian J., 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Diffie, Prof. Baily W., 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Dinnerstein, Prof. Leonard, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Drimmer, Prof. Melvin, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Dunn, Prof. Richard S., 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Dutka, Mr. Barry L., 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Etelstein, Prof. Melvin A., 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - England, Prof. J. Carter, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Epstein, Mr. Alan, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Eubank, Prof. Keith, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Fair, Theopolis, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Falk, Prof. Minna R., 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Falk Festschrift, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Falnes, Prof. Oscar J., 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Farnell, Prof. James E., 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Finegold, Dr. Henry L., 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Fineman, Clarise, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Ferguson, Prof. Wallace K., 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Ferguson - replacement, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Finkle, Dr. Lee, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Flaherty, Prof. John E., 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Flanders, Prof. Ralph, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Frieke, Mr. Ernest, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Funigiello, Prof. Phillip J., 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Gabel, Jack, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Gerves, Michael, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Glasner, Prof. John F., 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Goldman, Dr. Eric F., 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Goldman, Mr. Martin, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Gottdner, Mrs. Ruth, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Gotfried, Prof. Paul, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Gotlief, Prof. Beatrice, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Govin, Prof Thomas T., 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Greenlaw, Prof. Ralph, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Guinn, Prof. Paul, 1950-1970 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Hammond, Dr. Harold E., 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226332 0
  - Hauptman, Laurence M., 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Hellman, Doris, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Hemphill, Prof. John M., 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Herzstein, Dr. Robert E., 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Hester, Pres. James M., 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Hidy, Prof. Ralph W., 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Higgins, Prof. Trumbull, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Hindle, Dean Brooke, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Hulme, Harold, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Illick, Prof. Joseph E, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Irwin, Prof. Ray W., 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Israel, Jerry Michael, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Jackson, Prof. Frederick H., 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Jackson, Prof. Kenneth T., 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Johnson, Prof. Edgar N., 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Jones, Dr. Theodore F., 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Kaplow, Prof. Jeffrey J, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Katz, Irving, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Kelly, Dr. Daniel, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Kershner, Prof. Frederick, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Klebanow, Prof. Diana, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Kleinfeld, Dr. Gerald, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Kovaleff, Prof. Theodore, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Kriegel, Prof. Leonard, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Kroos, Prof. Herman E., 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Leder, Lawrence H., 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Lee, Dr. Ta-Ling, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Lehman, Dr. Orin, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Lewis, Miss Helena, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Lowenberg, Prof. Bert J., 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Lohrberg, Mr. Jack, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Luraghi, Dr. Raimundo, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Lurie, Prof. Edward, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - McCutchen, Prof Samuel P., 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - McDonnell, Prof. E.W., 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - McGuire, James E., 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Mahoney, Joseph, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Manuel, Prof. Frank, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Maxwell, Prof. Margaret, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Mathes, Prof. William, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Mayer, Arnold J., 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Mayer, H. Jack, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Meade, Dr. Robert O., 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Menashe, Prof. Louis, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Mendel, Prof. Arthur P., 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Mezvinsky, Mr. Norton, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Miller, Mr. Richard H., 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Mohl, Raymond A., 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Molotsi, Mr. Peter, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Moutafakis, Dr. George J., 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Musto, Ronald, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Nadler, Harry, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Nash, Gerald, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Noss, Dean Henry H. B, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Nugent, Walter T. K., 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - O'Brien, John, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - O'Callagher, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Ofonayoro, Walter I., 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - O'Keefe, Kevin, 1970-1976 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Olin, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Olson, Edwin, 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Owens, John B., 1950-1970 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Paolino, Ernest, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226333 8
  - Park, Dean Joseph, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Park, Dean Joseph- Replacement, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Parkes, Prof Henry B- American Civilization, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Parkes, Prof Henry B- Correspondence and Material, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Pascoe, Louis B (Fordham), 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Paul, Prof Arnold, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Platt, Hermann K, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Pruden, Prof Durward, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Prusak, Mr. Laurence, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Putney, Prof. W. Taylor, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Miss Rapone, Anita, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Rappaport, Prof Armin, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Reither, Prof Joseph, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Richardson, Prof James F, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Robinson, Dean Thomas P, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Rose, Prof Paul Lawrence, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Rosen, Prof Elliot A, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Ryan, Denis (Summer Session), 1976 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Salomone, Prof A. William, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Sayles, Prof George O, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Schlatter, Prof Richard, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Schmeller, Kurt Dr. (first term summer session), 1973 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Schmitt, Prof Hans A, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Sellen, Prof Robert W, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Skolnik, Prof Richard, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Smith, Carleton S. Prof., 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Smith, Prof Edward C, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Snyder, Prof Louis L, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Sokolsky, Mr. Wallace, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Solnick, Prof Bruce, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Solomon, Prof Howard, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Spann, Dr. Edward K, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Spencer, Joseph, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Stassin, Miss Daphney, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Steckmesser, Prof Kent L, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Stein, Mr Leon, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Sterling, Dr David, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Stevens, Prof Harry R, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Stiefel, Tina, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Still Party, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Stoianobich, Prof Traian, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Stojko, Wolldymyr, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Strauss, Gerald, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Tan, Prof Chester, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Thomson, Prof Edward P, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Tschevotarioff, Prof Bill V, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Vexler, Dr Robert, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Walden, Prof Daniel, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Wasserman, Dr Stanley, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Watts, Prof James F Jr, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Wegs, James Robert, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Weisberger, Prof Bernard A, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Wetterau, Prof James O, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Wheeler, Bennet Sir John, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Wheeler, Prof Robert H L, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Whiteman Jr, Prof Harold, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Wolfe- grading issue, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Wolfenden, Prof James W, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Yanow, Miss Lilli Ann, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Thesis Direction- Faculty Sponsorship of Theses, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226334 6
  - Fellowship Information, Awards etc, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Fellowship Information, Awards etc, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Fellowship Information, Awards etc, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Fellowship Announcement, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Woodrow Wilson Nominations For, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Awards, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Nominations, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Graduate Assistants, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Teaching Assistants, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Fulbright Hays Fellowship, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Woodrow Wilson Dissertation Fellowship, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Ford Foundation Dissertation Fellowship in Ethnic Studies, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Fellowship Award Nominees for all Awards, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Summary of Awards, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Fellowship Awards Summer, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Fellowship information (lists of applicants, general notices), undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Woodrow Wilson Dissertation Fellowship, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Woodrow Wilson Designate, undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - FPDA Proposal, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Teaching Assistantships, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - DAAD Fellowship, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Award by George J Schoengood to WSC History of Evening Division of School of Engineering, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Awards- Accepts and Declines, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Fulbrights, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Doctoral Dissertation in Natural Resources, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Spring Fellowship Materials, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - List of Applicants for Awards, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Teaching Assistant Files, General Rules, undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - W Wilson Dissertation Fellowship, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Alternates Still Interested, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - NDEA Title VI Grading Sheet, undated (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Fellowship Awards Procedures, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - DAAD, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Junior Fellowships Center for International Studies, undated (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Summer Scholarships, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Alternates Not Interested, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Summary of Awards, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Teaching Assistants Acceptances, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Woodrow Wilson, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Woodrow Wilson Dissertation Fellowship, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Pre-Doctoral Fellowships, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Spring Fellowships, 0000 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Wilson Dissertation Fellowships, 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - EPDA- Letters to Students on Program, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - EPDA- Program, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Education Professions Development Act, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Summary of Awards, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Awards- Accepts and Declines, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - EPDA- Part E Fellowship Program Correspondence, undated (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Fellowships, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Kent, undated (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Fulbright-Hayes, undated (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - German Academic Exchange Service Fellowship, undated (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Belgian American Educational Foundation, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - NDEA Title IV, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - NDEA Title IV Summer Tenure, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - NDEA Title IV, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - University Fellowships and Scholarships, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Ford MA- 3 Scholarship, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Lehman Fellowship Awards, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Herbert H Lehman Fellows, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Pre-Doctoral Fellows, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - King Fellowship, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Louis Lerner Scholarship, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - McKenzie Fellowship, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Penfield Fellowship, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - MDEA Title VI, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Summer Tuition Grant, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Woodrow Wilson Dissertation Fellowship Possibilities, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - NYS Regents Teaching Fellowships, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Teaching Assistantships, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Possible Assistants Emergency, undated (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Fellowship Awards and Responses, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Resident Fellows, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Fellowships and Financial Aid, undated (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - Summary of Awards and Responses, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - Teaching Assistants, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - Fellowships, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - Fellowship Award Letters, undated (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - NDEA, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - NDEA Title IV Fellows, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226335 3
  - Fellowship Information, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Fellowship Recommendations, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Special Fellowships, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Fellowship Opportunities, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Healey Award Nominee, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Incentive Award, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Work Study Program, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - GAS Research Fund, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Fellowships, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Fellowship Procedures, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Pre-Doctoral Fellows, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Fellowship Talk, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Rejection Letters, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Regents Fellowships, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Award Memo Forms, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Summer Awards, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Special Awards, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - NDEA Title IV Fellows Summer Program, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - NDEA Title VI, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Fellowship Procedures, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - 3rd Yr Assistantship, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Kent Danforth, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - DAAD, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Project Proposals from Stone, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Faculty Fellowships, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Fellowship Awards, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Fellowships, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Summer Tuition, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Application for NDEA Grant, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Ron Kirchun, NDEA, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - NDEA Title IV Awards, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - NDEA Title IV Grant, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - NDEA Title IV " Application as Submitted", 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - NDEA Title VI, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - NDEA Title IV Fellowship Program, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Grants for Research, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Promising Students, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Tudor, Stuart, undated (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Proposed Grad Assistants, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Assistants, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Candidates for Teaching Positions, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Faculty Appointment Possibilities, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Recruitment Faculty, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - London, Herbert (Recruitment), 1971 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Black Appointment, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Medical School Professorship, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - 16th cent recruitment, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Medieval Replacement, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Colonial Appt, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - New Appt, European, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Russian History, Personnel, 1958-1962 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Salomone, Replacement, 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Park Replacement, 1976-1957 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Colonial Replacement, undated (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - American Intellectual History, Candidates for Position in, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Barber, Eleonore, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Bernhardt, W, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Barry, Mary, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Chalmers, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Crowe, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Levy, Darleen GS, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Jaher, Frederick, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226336 1
  - Klein (Africa Position), 1965 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Lankford, 1961-1965 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Gershoy Replacement, 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Goez, W, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Goldman, Eric, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Gutman, Herbert G, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Hansen, K, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - John Jay Hurt, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Loewenberg, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Mandelbaum, 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Mosse, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Raucher, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Resnick, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Tarr, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Recruitment- Placement Dockets Returned, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Ringer, 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Gershoy, undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Portuguese Prof, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - American Civilization, 0000 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Woodman, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Coben, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Staudenraus, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Steckmesser MS, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Cockroft, Jes D, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Foreign Policy Job, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Udovitch, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Underdown, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Recruitment General, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Near Eastern History, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Govan, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Goodman, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - McCormick, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Thomson, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Turbow, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Thomas, T Wynant, Asian History, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Haight, Jeffrey, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Bank, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Dobbert, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Recruitment- Letters of Inquiry, 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Recruitment- Special, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Special Job Applicants, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Job Applicants, Summer School, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Afro-American Possibilities, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Bernhardt, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Hawke, D, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Replacement, undated (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Young, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Vyververg, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Recruitment, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - American Diplomats, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Bray- CHAS, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Sachser, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - McCaffrey, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Judson, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Black History Job, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Early National Recrutiment, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - English History Suggestion, 1966-1968 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Colonial, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Listing of Candidates, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Overfield, JH, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Negro Opponents, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Kenan Chair General, 1966-1968 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Hiss Science, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Franklin, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Genevese, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - For Emergency Appt, undated (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Graubard, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Stoianobich, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - Hess, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - Griffiths, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Hebrew History, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Toynbee, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - Wiseberger, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Recruitment AHA, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - Mayer, 1968-1971 (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - Hardach, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - Papa Cosma, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - WSC Position, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - Lach, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - Mator, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 85)
  - Hindle on Kenan Chair, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 86)
  - Kenan Chair, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 87)
  - Duberman, 1964-1969 (Box 12, Folder 88)
  - Beitzeld, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 90)
  - Kenan, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226337 9
  - Lensen GA, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Keddie, Nicki, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Recruitment Ad Hoc Committees, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Latin American Job, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Civil War Position, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Black Historians, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - American Urban Appointment, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Untitled, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Anderson, Karen, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226364 3
  - Asher, Nina, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Early, Frances, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Gilje, Paul A., undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Lenn, Myra C, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Greene, Rebecca S., undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Hampel, Robert L, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Herman, Debora, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Issermin, Maurice, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Kaufman, Janet E., undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Knee, Stuart, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)